<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on </title>
    <link>/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>I Wrote Another Book</title>
      <link>/posts/new-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/new-book/</guid>
      <description>Unveiling &amp;ldquo;Verses Under a Killing Moon&amp;rdquo;: A Journey Through The Macabre in Verse I&amp;rsquo;m thrilled to finally announce the release of my debut poetry collection, &amp;ldquo;Verses Under a Killing Moon&amp;rdquo;! This project has been a labor of love, pouring my heart and soul onto the page to explore themes of dark thoughts that run through your mind at night.&#xA;Verses Under a Killing Moon takes you on a journey through fear, paranoia, and loneliness with raw honesty and lyrical beauty.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gitkraken: Taming the Git Beast</title>
      <link>/posts/gitkraken/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 18:32:58 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/gitkraken/</guid>
      <description>GitKraken: Taming the Git Beast with a Visual Approach Imagine navigating a complex code jungle without a map or compass. That&amp;rsquo;s what using Git can feel like for many developers, especially beginners. Enter GitKraken, a visual Git client that aims to make version control intuitive and accessible for everyone.&#xA;At its core, GitKraken is a graphical user interface (GUI) for Git, the popular version control system. Instead of relying on cryptic commands and text-based interfaces, GitKraken presents a visual representation of your code&amp;rsquo;s history and branching structure.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI and the Butlerian Jihad</title>
      <link>/posts/dune-ai/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 12:29:51 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/dune-ai/</guid>
      <description>The End of Machines, the Rise of Man? Lessons from the Butlerian Jihad on AI Development In Frank Herbert&amp;rsquo;s Dune universe, the Butlerian Jihad stands as a stark cautionary tale about the dangers of artificial intelligence. This fictional war, fought millennia before the events of the main saga, resulted in a near-complete ban on thinking machines due to their perceived threat to humanity. While Dune is science fiction, the Butlerian Jihad offers valuable insights and warnings for our own burgeoning development of AI.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ruby on Rails vs. PHP Laravel</title>
      <link>/posts/laravel/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/laravel/</guid>
      <description>Ruby on Rails vs. PHP Laravel: Choosing the Right Weapon for Your Web Development Arsenal In the fast-paced world of web development, choosing the right framework can be the difference between a smooth sailing voyage and a storm-tossed journey. Ruby on Rails (RoR) and PHP Laravel are two heavyweight contenders in the framework ring, each boasting passionate followings and distinct strengths. But which one deserves a place in your development toolbox?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diving into Ruby: Unlocking the World of Programming</title>
      <link>/posts/ruby-funds/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 17:12:20 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/ruby-funds/</guid>
      <description>Diving into Ruby: Unlocking the World of Programming Ruby, with its quirky syntax and friendly community, has captivated programmers for decades. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a seasoned coder seeking a new tool or a curious newcomer wanting to build your first website, the fundamentals of Ruby offer a rewarding journey. So, grab your metaphorical shovel and let&amp;rsquo;s unearth the gems at the core of this vibrant language.&#xA;Hello, World! (With a Ruby Twist):</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How the Web Works</title>
      <link>/posts/how-the-web-works/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jan 2024 17:51:29 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/how-the-web-works/</guid>
      <description>Demystifying the Maze: How the Web Works We click, we scroll, we tap - the web is an ever-present companion, but have you ever wondered what goes on behind the scenes? Let&amp;rsquo;s peel back the curtain and explore the intricate machinery that brings websites to life.&#xA;From URL to Reality:&#xA;The Address Quest: Your journey begins with a simple URL, like &amp;ldquo;www.google.com&amp;rdquo;. But computers speak IP addresses, not fancy domain names.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My First Post</title>
      <link>/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 21:07:19 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>Welcome! This is my blog where I post about my thoughts on tech and other philisophical issues. I have previously written for Medium, and have had some tech blogs published to Dev Genius, and Her Campus. However, I have decided to exclusively publish my thoughts on this site instead.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
